http://www.stanleymonitor.com/policies.php

LTE
CellularMedical Alarm MonitoringRadio Mesh NetworkSupported TechnologiesVideo Verification Monitoring
SERVICES
View AllDealer ToolsDevelopmentPersonalized SupportVendor Partners
NEWS
BlogCase StudiesDealer IncentivesEvents CalendarIndustry NewsStay Connected
Our Policies & Disclaimers
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy applies to information collected, used and disclosed by Stanley Black and Decker, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively referred to as Stanley Black and Decker) in connection with information that we collect
Through our websites, microsites, mobile sites operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (the Sites), Through our software applications made available by for use on or through computers and mobile devices (the Apps),
Through our social media pages and apps that we control from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (collectively referred to as our Social Media Pages), Through HTML formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy, Offline such as when you visit our stores or retail kiosks, attend a tradeshow,
or place an order or request for support over the phone.
Complete Global Privacy Policy Website Terms of UseStanley Black & Decker, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies, including Stanley Security Solutions, Inc., Stanley Convergent Security Solutions, Inc., Sargent & Greenleaf, Inc. and Stanley Access Technologies, LLC (collectively and alternatively, “STANLEY” or the “Stanley family”), own, operate and/or control a global network of websites and web pages, including stanleysecuritysolutions.webpagefxstage.com (collectively the “Sites”). These Sites are provided to visitors and users of the Sites (collectively, “you” or “your”) only if you agree to these Terms of Use unconditionally and without modification. Your use of any of the Sites constitutes your acceptance and agreement to all these terms and conditions. Additional terms and conditions may apply to your use of eServices, purchases of goods or services (see our Standard Terms and Conditions of Sale located at https://www.stanleysecuritysolutions.com/legal.html, and to specific portions or features of the Sites (such as sweepstakes or public forums), all of which are incorporated into these Terms of Use. You will be bound by such additional terms should you use the specific features or portions of the Sites. If these additional terms conflict with these Terms of Use, the additional terms shall apply. PLEASE TAKE THE TIME TO READ ALL TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SITES. By accessing, registering on or otherwise using any of the Sites, you unconditionally agree to these Terms of Use whether you have read them. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, you may not access, view or use the Sites.
Complete Website Terms of Use Terms and ConditionsUnless and to the extent that a separate contract executed between the purchaser (“Customer”) and SCSS applies, the purchase of goods and services by Customer (“Order”) will be governed solely by these General Terms and Conditions of Sale, whether or not these General Terms and Conditions of Sale are referenced in the Order. Except as provided in the “Orders” section below, all provisions on the Order and all other documents submitted by Customer are expressly rejected. SCSS will not be deemed to have waived these Terms and Conditions of Sale if it fails to object to provisions submitted by Customer. Customer’s silence or acceptance or use of the goods and services is acceptance of these Terms and Conditions of Sale. Any modification or addition to these Terms and Conditions of Sale must be in writing and signed by an authorized representative of Customer and SCSS.
Complete Terms and Conditions
Go Back
Your accounts in your hand
STANLEY Security offers the ability to remotely access your account information, through our mobile application - MASmobile. Learn more.LEARN MORE
Supported Technologies
STANLEY Security works with its vendor partners to offer you the services your customers request and need in this ever changing marketplace.
LEARN MORE
1.800.932.3304
Memphis Facility - 1341 Sycamore View Road, Suite 300, Memphis, TN 38134 Lacey Facility - 4500 3rd Avenue SE, Lacey, WA 98500 Plymouth Facility - 6000 Nathan Lane N, Plymouth, MN 55442 Indianapolis Facility - 8350 Sunlight Drive, Fishers, IN 46037
© STANLEY Security -
- All Rights Reserved
Site by www.chrisalford.com
